[
    {
        "front": "はります|",
        "back": "put up, poste, paste",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "かけます||",
        "back": "hang",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "かざります|",
        "back": "display, decorate",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "ならべます||",
        "back": "arrange, line up",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "うえます||",
        "back": "plant",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "もどします|",
        "back": "return, punt ~ back",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "まとめます||",
        "back": "put ~ together, put ~ in shape, sum up",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "しまいます|",
        "back": "put (things) away",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "きめます||",
        "back": "decide",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "よしゅうします|||",
        "back": "prepare one's lesson",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "ふくしゅうします||| ",
        "back": "review one's lesson",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "そのままにします|||",
        "back": "leave things as they are",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅぎょう ",
        "back": "class",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "こうぎ ",
        "back": "lecture",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "ミーティング",
        "back": "meeting",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "よてい ",
        "back": "plan, schedule",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "おしらせ ",
        "back": "notice",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "ガイドブック",
        "back": "guidebook",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "カレンダー ",
        "back": "calendar",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "ポスター ",
        "back": "poster",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "よていひょう",
        "back": "schedule",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "ごみばこ ",
        "back": "trash can, dustbin",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "にんぎょう ",
        "back": "doll",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "かびん ",
        "back": "vase",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "かがみ ",
        "back": "mirror",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "ひきだし ",
        "back": "drawer",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "げんかん ",
        "back": "front door, porch, entrance hall",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "ろうか ",
        "back": "corridor, hallway",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "かべ ",
        "back": "wall",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "いけ ",
        "back": "pond",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "もとのところ ",
        "back": "original place",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "まわり ",
        "back": "round, around",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "まんなか＊ ",
        "back": "center",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "すみ ",
        "back": "corner",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "まだ ",
        "back": "still",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "リュック",
        "back": "rucksack",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "ひじょうぶくろ",
        "back": "emergency kit",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "ひじょうじ",
        "back": "emergency ",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "せいかつ",
        "back": "live",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "かいちゅうでんとう",
        "back": "torch, flashlight",
        "chapter": 30
    },
    {
        "front": "～とか、～とか",
        "back": "~, ~, and so on",
        "chapter": 30
    }
]